// Creating an array and passing the number, questions, options and answer
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which among the following is a suitable term for the state of economy in which economic activity is slowing down but wages and prices continue to rise ?",
        answer: "Stagflation",
        options: ["Inflation",
            "Deflation",
            "Skweflation",
            "Stagflation"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which among the following imposes a greater burden (relative to resources) on the poor than on the rich ?",
        answer: "Regressive Tax",
        options: ["Progressive tax",
            "Regressive Tax",
            "Lump Sum tax",
            "Proportional tax"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which among the following phrases generally denotes National Income?",
        answer: "Net National Product at Factor Cost",
        options: ["Gross National Product at Market Prices",
            "Net National Product at Market Prices",
            "Gross National Product at Factor Cost",
            "Net National Product at Factor Cost"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "In context with the macroeconomics , Philips Curve is a relationship between the rates of ___?",
        answer: "Unemployment and Inflation",
        options: ["Unemployment & Exim trade",
            "Unemployment and Inflation",
            "Unemployment and Demand",
            "Unemployment and Poverty"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Which among the following is used for a situation of â€œToo much money chasing too few goods?",
        answer: "Demand Pull Inflation",
        options: ["Demand Pull Inflation",
            "Cost pull inflation",
            "Stagflation",
            "Hyperinflation"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "In economy, which among the following can be measured by calculating concentration ratios?",
        answer: "Competition",
        options: ["Devlopment",
            "Inflation",
            "Competition",
            "Social Security"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Which of the following items is characterised by highest income elasticity of demand among others?",
        answer: "Car",
        options: ["Car",
            "Milk",
            "Paddy",
            "Tobacco"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Which one of the following is NOT a sign of economic development?",
        answer: "Larger capital inflows",
        options: ["Changing structure of GDP in favour of industry",
            "Larger share of GDP coming from primary sector",
            "Larger capital inflows",
            "Institutional changes in an economy"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "A Goldilocks economy is represented by __:",
        answer: "Low Inflation, Steady economic growth",
        options: ["Low Inflation , High Economic Growth",
            "High Inflation, Low Economic Growth",
            "Low Inflation, Steady economic growth",
            "High Inflation, High Economic Growth"]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "The central Statistical Office (CSO) has started measuring economic growth by gross value-added (GVA) at basic prices, replacing the practice of measuring it by GDP at factor cost. What is the difference between GDP at factor cost and GVA at basic prices?",
        answer: "Production taxes are included and production subsidies excluded from GVA at basic prices",
        options: ["Production taxes are included and production subsidies excluded from GVA at basic prices",
            "Production taxes are excluded and production subsidies included in GVA at basic prices",
            "Production taxes and production subsidies included in GVA at basic prices",
            "Production taxes and production subsidies excluded from GVA at basic prices"
        ]
    }
]